<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-US"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/myblogs/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/myblogs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-US" /><updated>2022-12-26T20:14:48+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/myblogs/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Blogs</title><subtitle>description</subtitle><author><name>rs</name></author><entry><title type="html">What You Hide</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/myblogs/general/mystery/review/2022/12/26/what-you-hide-book-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What You Hide" /><published>2022-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/myblogs/general/mystery/review/2022/12/26/what-you-hide-book-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/myblogs/general/mystery/review/2022/12/26/what-you-hide-book-review/"><![CDATA[<p>Note: This book WILL change the way you view the library.</p>

<p>What You Hide is a thriller mystery told from two point of views: Mallory, who is homeless after running away from home to escape her creepy stepfather, and Spencer, a privileged teen who’s stuck doing community service because he tried to climb its brick exterior. They both have their own troubles, but they form an unexpected bond between them when they cross paths in the library. However, the library isn’t as safe as it seems. After the death of a woman in the library, strange things start happening; black footprints and creepy messages start appearing, and worse…there’s wailing at night.</p>

<p>I low-key believed in ghosts for a hot-minute, towards the end.</p>

<p>I consider myself a logical person: I love the sanctity of cause and effect, knowing there is a reason for everything in this universe. So when I say this was messing with me, it really was.</p>

<p>The book wasn’t what I thought it was going to be. I went in thinking this would be a plot-driven story, like most mysteries are, but I was pleasantly surprised at the amount of character development. Because of the multiple POVs in this book, we are able to get a glimpse into Mallory’s home life, and know that she was originally going to escape her controlling stepfather with her pregnant mother who ultimately chickened out and because she wasn’t ready. Likewise, we know that Spencer was adopted by a rich white family and literally has the world at his fingertips. However, he doesn’t know what he wants to do with his life and feels guilty knowing that he could’ve easily ended up in much worse circumstances.</p>

<p>That being said: there wasn’t much action in the book. I wasn’t at the edge of my seat for the whole book, more like the last 40 pages.</p>

<p>Beyond that, let’s back up for a minute and discuss Spencer and Mallory. Mallory is homeless, and Spencer is extremely privileged. I honestly don’t see how they work. It’s not that I don’t think them being friends is unrealistic. I just think the author could’ve done a better job building up their relationship, because honestly, it seemed one dimensional when I was reading it. Also, in real life, I doubt that their whole relationship would even have happened. When you are strapped for cash, don’t know when your next meal is, and have no idea where you’re going to sleep that night, in my opinion, that leaves very little mental space to think about romance. Likewise, I personally find it a little unrealistic that Spencer could’ve fallen for a girl in Mallory’s predicament; I don’t mean to undermine his character, but given his wealthy status, the author didn’t do much to help make their attraction to each other believable. It was just sort of there, more out of convenience than actual appreciation for who the other is.</p>

<p>Overall, the book for me was enjoyable. One could easily get entranced in this world that Natalie D. Richards created. It just wasn’t great like her other book Five Total Strangers, but I liked the idea of the story. This book would be a great choice for teens during Halloween to get into the spooky spirit!</p>]]></content><author><name>rs</name></author><category term="General" /><category term="Mystery" /><category term="Review" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: This book WILL change the way you view the library.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/myblogs/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/myblogs/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>